[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "quote": "Love is that condition in which the happiness of another person is essential to your own.",
    "author": "Robert A. Heinlein"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "quote": "If I had a flower for every time I thought of you… I could walk through my garden forever.",
    "author": "Alfred Tennyson"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "quote": "When you realize you want to spend the rest of your life with somebody, you want the rest of your life to start as soon as possible.",
    "author": "When Harry Met Sally"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "quote": "Each friend represents a world in us, a world possibly not born until they arrive, and it is only by this meeting that a new world is born.",
    "author": "Anais Nin"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "quote": "If you remember me, then I don’t care if everyone else forgets.",
    "author": "Haruki Murakami"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "quote": "Being deeply loved by someone gives you strength, while loving someone deeply gives you courage.",
    "author": "Lao Tzu"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "quote": "Let us be grateful to the people who make us happy; they are the charming gardeners who make our souls blossom.",
    "author": "Marcel Proust"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "quote": "There is nothing on this earth more to be prized than true friendship.",
    "author": "homas Aquinas"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "quote": "Being a family means you are a part of something very wonderful. It means you will love and be loved for the rest of your life.",
    "author": "Lisa Weed"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "quote": "I would rather spend one lifetime with you, than face all the ages of this world alone.",
    "author": "J.K.K. Tolken"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "quote": "To be your friend was all I ever wanted; to be your lover was all I ever dreamed.",
    "author": "Valerie Lombardo"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "quote": "Romance is thinking about your significant other, when you are supposed to be thinking about something else.",
    "author": "Nicholas Sparks"
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "quote": "What’s so hard about love? You simply grab the other’s hand and refuse to let go.",
    "author": "Boys Over Flowers"
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "quote": "Once upon a time there was a boy who loved a girl and her laughter was a question he wanted to spend his whole life answering.",
    "author": "The History Of Love"
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "quote": "Take love, multiply it by infinity and take it to the depths of forever, and you still have only a glimpse of how I feel for you.",
    "author": "Meet Joe Black"
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "quote": "I love you because the entire universe conspired to help me find you.",
    "author": "The Alchemist"
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "quote": "Everyone has a friend during each stage of life. But only lucky ones have the same friend in all stages of life.",
    "author": "Unknown"
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "quote": "There is a madness in loving you, a lack of reason that makes it feel so flawless.",
    "author": "Leo Christopher"
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "quote": "He stepped down, trying not to look long at her, as if she were the sun, yet he saw her, like the sun, even without looking.",
    "author": "Leo Tolstoy"
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "quote": "If ever there is tomorrow when we’re not together…there is something you must always remember. You are braver than you believe, stronger than you seem, and smarter than you think but the most important thing is, even if we’re apart… I’ll always be with you.",
    "author": "Winnie the Pooh"
  }
]